[
    {
        "question": "Who was the first American-born president?",
        "answer": "Martin Van Buren"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which president made Christmas a national holiday?",
        "answer": "Ulysses S. Grant"
    },
    {
        "question": "“Old Whitey” was the beloved horse of which president?",
        "answer": "Zachary Taylor"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which president was a classically trained pianist and played 4 other instruments?",
        "answer": "Richard Nixon"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who was the first and only U.S. president to serve non-consecutive terms?",
        "answer": "Grover Cleveland"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which president signed the act creating the United States Marine Band?",
        "answer": "John Adams"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which president and his wife attended Napoleon‘s coronation at Notre Dame Cathedral?",
        "answer": "James Monroe"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who was the first president to have written a biography of another president?",
        "answer": "Herbert Hoover"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which president had turned down offers to play professional football?",
        "answer": "Gerald Ford"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who was the first president to attend baseball’s opening day and throw the ceremonial first pitch?",
        "answer": "William Howard Taft"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which president and his wife received a Siamese cat as a gift from the American consul of Bangkok?",
        "answer": "Rutherford B. Hayes"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which president was often mocked in the press for his unkempt appearance?",
        "answer": "Abraham Lincoln"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which president hired Louis C. Tiffany—first design director of Tiffany and Co.—for a massive renovation of the White House and its private chambers?",
        "answer": "Chester A. Arthur"
    },
    {
        "question": "Though three presidents (Adams, Jefferson, and Monroe) died on the 4th of July, which president was the only president to have been born on that date?",
        "answer": "Calvin Coolidge"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which president and his wife met in the fifth grade, were high school sweethearts, but did not marry until their mid-thirties?",
        "answer": "Harry S. Truman"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which president hated his painted portrait so much that he eventually burned it?",
        "answer": "Theodore Roosevelt"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which president put up the first Christmas tree in the White House?",
        "answer": "Benjamin Harrison"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which president donated all of his presidential salary (and his congressional salary before that) to charity?",
        "answer": "John F. Kennedy"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which president and his wife hold the record for longest married first couple?",
        "answer": "Jimmy Carter"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who was the first president to ride in a car to his inauguration?",
        "answer": "Warren G. Harding"
    }
]
